question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The Sun rises from the North.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
